ATIP NASAKUN

Reserved Officers Training Corps Course (ROTC)

Email atipnasakun.work@gmai.com **Phone** 0956202061 Github https://github.com/atippaz

Summary

Have experience in programming and setting up systems in various formats such as Web Application, Automation and other types of programs that can solve problems. I want to be a system developer who can edit and create anything. I want. Ready to learn new technology all the time.

Experience

10X Plus Co., Ltd

FullStack Developer | Nest / Nuxt3

July 2024 - Present

- maintain ERP Software Upgrade Project nuxt2 to nuxt 3 in 1 month
- Upgrade Legacy Nestjs to new version
- automate deploy process using gitlab
- · Create a landing Page and BookingSystem

ClickNext Company Limited

Full-Stack Developer Vue3 / C# ASP.net

May 2023 - March 2024 (11 Month)

- · Developed a CRUD system such as a visit job tracking.
- Exported and imported data to and from the system using Excel files.
- · Created a system for merging customer data.
- Created a script for code analysis and code review for C# with Roslyn.

Superdev CO., LTD

Frontend Developer

June 2022 - June 2023 (1 Year)

- Work with a team, have meetings, and divide projects into pages to help each other.
- Completed tasks according to Figma designs.

10X Plus Co., Ltd

Frontend Developer

June 2021 - January 2022 (6 Month)

Developed ERP system by integrating data from APIs and displaying it on the website.

Projects

Simple Inventory Stock System (Nuxt3, Nest, Mysql,Line Api)

- Developed a system to track the import and usage of goods, storing them in batches with cost prices.
- Implemented average cost price calculation when issuing goods and integrated with Line Message API for issuing alerts.
- Classified goods by SKU to accommodate multiple product types.

Bad Boys (Vue SPA, Express, MongoDB)

- Developed a mobile-friendly badminton pairing application using Vue SPA.
- Designed to solve the problem of manually pairing players during badminton games with friends by randomly assigning pairs.
- · Deployed the application on Vercel for easy access and use.

32 Game Controller (Arduino, Nginx, Vue, Express, Docker)

- · Developed an online game controllable via ESP32, integrating the ESP32 with the game server through Express to control the website using Socket.
- Created a two-player XO game with spectator mode, allowing others to watch the game in real-time.
- Combined various techniques and deployed the project with a custom domain at atipnasakun.online.

Activities

Hackatrain By DevMountain #2

11 November 2022 -12 November 2022

- · Created a program convert data csv to xml and xml to csv without library
- · Chat App with Vue (web socket)

Education

King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok

Mathematics Computer Science (MC) GPX 3.18 | May 2024

Skills

Frontend

Backend

- Vue / Nuxt
- ASP.net Core (C#)
- React / Remix / Next Express / Nest
- Angular

Other

Database

- IOT (Arduino)
- SQL Server
- Nginx
- MySQL
- Docker (Compose)
- MongoDB
- Desktop Application
- VPS Cloud Computer
- Http/Web Socket
- · Basic Deployment